This blade has a dark past.
It has shed much innocent blood.
You're a fool for traveling alone, so completely unprepared.
You're lucky your blood's still flowing.
Thank you.
So... what brings you to the land of the gatekeepers?
I'm searching for someone.
Someone very dear? A kindred spirit?
A dragon.
A dangerous quest for a lone hunter.
I've been looking for a long time.
It was winter...
I found him in the town square.
He was wounded, shivering in the cold.
I nursed him back to health and named him Scales.
He learned to fly quickly.
We were inseparable.
Then one afternoon... a giant shadow crossed the sun.
A massive dragon swept down and took him away.
Scales!
I swore I would find him, no matter how far I had to walk.
Across deserts, through ruined cities, across oceans.
Be careful in the deep caverns. Dragons remember who hurt them.
Scales? Is that you?
No... no, it can't be!
What have I done... Scales... I'm so sorry...